<List__Manager id="1">
  <animeList id="2">
    <Anime id="3">
      <name>Code Geass: Lelouch of the Rebellion</name>
      <id>1575</id>
      <score>8.83</score>
      <numEp>25</numEp>
      <finishedAiring>true</finishedAiring>
      <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/5/50331.jpg</image>
      <keyWords id="4">
        <string>year</string>
        <string>Empire</string>
        <string>nation</string>
        <string>conquest</string>
        <string>defeat</string>
        <string>resistance</string>
        <string>attempt</string>
        <string>independence</string>
        <string>prince</string>
        <string>crossfire</string>
        <string>timely</string>
        <string>appearance</string>
        <string>girl</string>
        <string>Power</string>
        <string>newfound</string>
        <string>power</string>
        <string>obedience</string>
        <string>journey</string>
        <string>vigilante</string>
        <string>order</string>
        <string>revenge</string>
      </keyWords>
      <synopsis>In the year 2010, the Holy Empire of Britannia is establishing itself as a dominant military nation, starting with the conquest of Japan. Renamed to Area 11 after its swift defeat, Japan has seen significant resistance against these tyrants in an attempt to regain independence.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Lelouch Lamperouge, exiled prince of Britannia, unfortunately finds himself caught in a crossfire between the two nations&amp;#039; armed forces. He is able to escape, however, thanks to the timely appearance of a mysterious girl named C.C., who bestows upon him Geass, the &amp;quot;Power of Kings.&amp;quot; Realizing the vast potential of his newfound &amp;quot;power of absolute obedience,&amp;quot; Lelouch embarks upon a perilous journey as the masked vigilante known as Zero, leading a merciless onslaught against Britannia in order to get revenge once and for all.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
    </Anime>
    <Anime id="5">
      <name>Death Note</name>
      <id>1535</id>
      <score>8.71</score>
      <numEp>37</numEp>
      <finishedAiring>true</finishedAiring>
      <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/9/9453.jpg</image>
      <keyWords id="6">
        <string>god</string>
        <string>death</string>
        <string>face</string>
        <string>name</string>
        <string>notebook</string>
        <string>Death</string>
        <string>lifestyle</string>
        <string>human</string>
        <string>use</string>
        <string>Death</string>
        <string>human</string>
        <string>realm</string>
        <string>school</string>
        <string>student</string>
        <string>prodigy</string>
        <string>Light</string>
        <string>Death</string>
        <string>state</string>
        <string>notebook</string>
        <string>name</string>
        <string>experiment</string>
        <string>Death</string>
        <string>Light</string>
        <string>power</string>
        <string>capability</string>
        <string>Light</string>
        <string>order</string>
        <string>world</string>
        <string>crime</string>
        <string>worship</string>
        <string>discover</string>
        <string>serial</string>
        <string>killer</string>
        <string>consequently</string>
        <string>apprehend</string>
        <string>count</string>
        <string>assistance</string>
        <string>detective</string>
        <string>world:</string>
        <string>man</string>
        <string>name</string>
      </keyWords>
      <synopsis>A shinigami, as a god of death, can kill any person&amp;mdash;provided they see their victim&amp;#039;s face and write their victim&amp;#039;s name in a notebook called a Death Note. One day, Ryuk, bored by the shinigami lifestyle and interested in seeing how a human would use a Death Note, drops one into the human realm.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
High school student and prodigy Light Yagami stumbles upon the Death Note and&amp;mdash;since he deplores the state of the world&amp;mdash;tests the deadly notebook by writing a criminal&amp;#039;s name in it. When the criminal dies immediately following his experiment with the Death Note, Light is greatly surprised and quickly recognizes how devastating the power that has fallen into his hands could be.            &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
With this divine capability, Light decides to extinguish all criminals in order to build a new world where crime does not exist and people worship him as a god. Police, however, quickly discover that a serial killer is targeting criminals and, consequently, try to apprehend the culprit. To do this, the Japanese investigators count on the assistance of the best detective in the world: a young and eccentric man known only by the name of L.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
    </Anime>
    <Anime id="7">
      <name>One Piece</name>
      <id>21</id>
      <score>8.58</score>
      <numEp>0</numEp>
      <finishedAiring>false</finishedAiring>
      <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/6/73245.jpg</image>
      <keyWords id="8">
        <string>Pirate</string>
        <string>capture</string>
        <string>death</string>
        <string>Government</string>
        <string>change</string>
        <string>death</string>
        <string>existence</string>
        <string>treasure</string>
        <string>world</string>
        <string>revelation</string>
        <string>amount</string>
        <string>pinnacle</string>
        <string>glory</string>
        <string>title</string>
        <string>Enter</string>
        <string>boy</string>
        <string>standard</string>
        <string>definition</string>
        <string>persona</string>
        <string>wicked</string>
        <string>pirate</string>
        <string>reason</string>
        <string>pirate</string>
        <string>adventure</string>
        <string>childhood</string>
        <string>crew</string>
        <string>travel</string>
        <string>adventures</string>
        <string>enemies</string>
        <string>order</string>
      </keyWords>
      <synopsis>Gol D. Roger was known as the &amp;quot;Pirate King,&amp;quot; the strongest and most infamous being to have sailed the Grand Line. The capture and death of Roger by the World Government brought a change throughout the world. His last words before his death revealed the existence of the greatest treasure in the world, One Piece. It was this revelation that brought about the Grand Age of Pirates, men who dreamed of finding One Piece&amp;mdash;which promises an unlimited amount of riches and fame&amp;mdash;and quite possibly the pinnacle of glory and the title of the Pirate King.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Enter Monkey D. Luffy, a 17-year-old boy who defies your standard definition of a pirate. Rather than the popular persona of a wicked, hardened, toothless pirate ransacking villages for fun, Luffy&amp;rsquo;s reason for being a pirate is one of pure wonder: the thought of an exciting adventure that leads him to intriguing people and ultimately, the promised treasure. Following in the footsteps of his childhood hero, Luffy and his crew travel across the Grand Line, experiencing crazy adventures, unveiling dark mysteries and battling strong enemies, all in order to reach the most coveted of all fortunes&amp;mdash;One Piece.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
    </Anime>
    <Anime id="9">
      <name>The Pet Girl of Sakurasou</name>
      <id>13759</id>
      <score>8.4</score>
      <numEp>24</numEp>
      <finishedAiring>true</finishedAiring>
      <image>https://myanimelist.cdn-dena.com/images/anime/4/43643.jpg</image>
      <keyWords id="10">
        <string>conscience</string>
        <string>force</string>
        <string>year</string>
        <string>move</string>
        <string>satellite</string>
        <string>dorm</string>
        <string>misfit</string>
        <string>turn</string>
        <string>life</string>
        <string>average</string>
        <string>collection</string>
        <string>dorm</string>
        <string>Misaki</string>
        <string>animator;</string>
        <string>playwright</string>
        <string>dorm</string>
        <string>manager</string>
        <string>art</string>
        <string>party</string>
        <string>girl</string>
        <string>friend</string>
        <string>year</string>
        <string>student</string>
        <string>voice</string>
        <string>actress</string>
        <string>move</string>
        <string>desire</string>
        <string>infantile</string>
        <string>year</string>
        <string>world-class</string>
        <string>mangaka</string>
        <string>spring</string>
        <string>trimester</string>
        <string>trigger</string>
        <string>change</string>
        <string>light</string>
        <string>novel</string>
        <string>name</string>
        <string>talent</string>
        <string>friendship</string>
        <string>cast</string>
      </keyWords>
      <synopsis>When abandoned kittens and his good conscience force second year Sorata Kanda to move into Suimei High School&amp;rsquo;s infamous Sakura Hall, the satellite dorm and its eccentric, misfit residents turn his life upside down. The decidedly average Sorata finds it difficult to fit in with the bizarre collection of dorm residents like Misaki, an energetic animator; Jin, a playwright playboy; Ryuunosuke, a reclusive programmer; and Chihiro, the dorm manager, art teacher, and party girl.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Sorata&apos;s friend Nanami, a second year student and aspiring voice actress, pushes him to find new owners for the many cats so that he can quickly move back into the regular dorms. However, his desire to escape Sakura Hall wavers when the pet-like and infantile second year Mashiro Shiina, a world-class artistic savant looking to become a mangaka, transfers in during the spring trimester and quickly latches onto him.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Supported by each other&apos;s quirks, Sorata and Mashiro come out of their shells and trigger change in the lives of those around them. Based on the light novel series of the same name, [i]Sakurasou no Pet na Kanojo[/i] explores the fine threads connecting talent, hard work, romance, and friendship with its ensemble cast.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
[Written by MAL Rewrite]</synopsis>
    </Anime>
  </animeList>
  <suggestionList id="11"/>
</List__Manager>